gamexn.net 2013-01-18

# Privacy policy - GameXN

GameXN PRIVACY POLICY

The policy below applies to the following: [www.gamexn.com](http://www.gamexn.com/) and all their respective sub-domains, and any other website operated by GameXN (collectively “Sites”), as well as the GameXN GO games app (“Games App”) and the games and other content products operated by GameXN that are available on the Sites and Games App. We may refer to the Sites, the Games App, and such games and other content products collectively as our “GameXN Network”. “GameXN”, “we” or “us” refers to GameXN AS.

OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage, the Games App, and, in general, at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Please understand that by accessing or using the GameXN Network you are agreeing with the privacy policy terms. As a result, we encourage you to read this entire Privacy Policy. If at any time you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [www.gamexn.com/ContactUs](http://www.gamexn.com/ContactUs). 

WHAT INFORMATION MIGHT WE COLLECT and HOW MAY IT BE USED?

Sites and Games App

On some pages, you can play games, register and/or create a user profile, make requests, submit information, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include; name, email address, as well as other similar personal information. 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. In these circumstances, the types of personal information collected may be; name and/or online moniker.

We do store your personally identifiable information in a secure manner. We may also collect unique usage information, which does NOT include personally identifiable information, to assist us in understanding our customers' use patterns and for use in developing new products and services.

Games

When you play a game on the GameXN Network, GameXN collects certain profile information that you provide directly. We may automatically collect information about your game play and interactions with other players in a social game. Otherwise, games we operate on the GameXN Network do NOT collect personally identifiable information without your consent. 

Aggregated and Anonymous Data

We may also collect unique device usage information, which does NOT include personally identifiable information, to assist us in understanding our customers' use patterns and for use in developing new products and services. To facilitate the operation of the Games App, it will collect and report anonymous information necessary to ensure reliable delivery of downloaded games and game content. This information may include data about whether or not content download and installation was successful, game session length (for trial versions), and Games App session length. To help ensure that you have consistent, high quality experiences with our games, and to assist us with product development and planning, we do collect anonymous usage statistics. We do this by assigning a unique identifier in our databases that is NOT linked to any of your personal information. The information gathered is used to accurately count the number of people using our games and other content successfully and is also NOT linked to any of your personal information. At times we may share this usage information with third parties, but only in an anonymous aggregated form - that is, we collect usage information about the thousands of times our games are played, and analyze it as a whole. 

Social Networks

When you access any game on the GameXN Network at a social network (for example, Facebook), you permit GameXN to access certain information from your profile on that social network, depending on the game, as well as the privacy settings you have established for that social network. By playing a game on the GameXN Network through a social network, you are authorizing GameXN to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information that you agreed the social network could provide to GameXN through the social network application programming interface. 

Support

When you request support from us by email, on the telephone, through our web support portal, or by other means we may provide, we will collect and store the contact information you provide (generally your name and e-mail address), information about your game play or activity on the GameXN Network, any registration numbers you provide, as well as the communications between us over such support issue. 

With Whom Do We Share Personal Information?

We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent (subject to the limited exceptions identified below) and at the time you are asked for this information or for consent, we will inform you of: 

  * The personally identifiable information to be shared
  * The identity of the third party
  * A link to the third party's privacy statement, if available

Please understand that we may also share your information with third parties under the following limited circumstances and as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy: 

  * If we use third party contractors to provide services to us or on our behalf. For example, we might retain a company to email information about special offers, or to analyze data. We do require such contractors to maintain personally identifiable information as confidential, and to only use it on our behalf.
  * If we, in good faith, are required to disclose it to comply with legal processes, or we need to do so to protect your, our or the public's rights or property interests.
  * If our company is involved in a sale, merger, or any other combination with a third party. In such circumstances, the surviving entity will be responsible for this Privacy Policy and the personally identifiable information collected from you.

Does GameXN Use Passive Means To Collect Information?

To permit your efficient use of the GameXN Network, we use cookies (small files stored in your computer), which let us know how you accessed us and let us know that you are a prior customer (so that you will not have to re-enter all of the information previously provided to us every time you access our sites). We (or third parties on our behalf) may also use web beacons, or similar technologies, which are transparent images that have been placed on a web page or an e-mail message, and send a signal that allows us to determine when a page has been visited, or an e-mail opened. Web beacons or similar technologies do not contain or collect personally identifiable information. The information that we do collect is used to allow us to better understand our customers' usage patterns, and to help us determine how they accessed our website(s). This information, in turn, allows us to improve our products to better meet your needs, and to enhance our communications with you. 

Are there other Parties Collecting Information about me that I should be aware of while using the GameXN Network?

Advertisers and Ad Network

If and when GameXN carries advertisements on the GameXN Network. Some of these ads are served by GameXN, and some are served by third party ad networks. Where an ad is served by GameXN that requests personal information from you (for example, in a survey), GameXN collects the personal information you disclose, along with the advertiser and/or ad network. Otherwise, GameXN does not collect personal information from such ads. 

Some ads may provide the ability to click through to websites or properties run by the advertiser or other third parties or to otherwise interact with an advertiser, sometimes without even leaving the Sites. GameXN is not responsible for the privacy practices of advertisers. Once you have clicked on an advertisement, you should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to determine how it handles any personally identifiable information it collects from you.

Ad networks and other third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to various websites other than the GameXN Network. GameXN does not have control over cookies, web beacons or other technologies that such third parties may use, but GameXN may acquire non-personally identifiable information regarding the behavior and usage patterns of users of websites and other online properties from third parties, and also may combine this information with other non-personally identifiable information we have collected, to deliver advertisements to you, measure the effectiveness of ads, and more effectively target advertisements and offerings that may be of greater interest to you. We are not responsible for the information collection practices of other third party websites that you may visit. Some of these third party websites and advertising companies may permit you to opt out of tracking by participating websites. GameXN is not responsible for the terms of these organizations or the effectiveness of their opt out procedures.

Other Third Parties

GameXN, or third party advertisers, may use third party research firms to conduct brand studies or perform other analytics, and such third party research firms may also use cookies or use beacons to gather relevant information, including whether a user has or has not seen a particular ad campaign. 

Do You Provide Ongoing Product Updates Or Other Information?

Periodically, we may send e-mails or service messages to users of our products and services with news, updates, special offers and other information relating to our products and services, and to select third party products and services. 

What Happens If I Decline To Provide Personal Information Or Remove Or Reject Passive Information Gathering?

If you choose not to submit personal information, or if you choose to configure your browser to remove or reject cookies or other passive data collection, you will not be able to fully utilize our products, services and website features (for example, you may not be able to receive digital items provided by an advertiser). 

How do we Protect the Information we Collect?

We use reasonable physical, technical, and administrative measures to safeguard personally identifiable information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification. For example, passwords and other sensitive information are encrypted in transit. We also take steps to ensure that only those GameXN employees, agents, and contractors who have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your personally identifiable information are granted access. 

When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card information), we encrypt that information using secure sockets layering technology (SSL), an industry standard protocol for billing transmission in order to protect the financial information you send us. We store your payment information in encrypted form.

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches of the Sites and our customer databases and records, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We want you to feel confident using the GameXN Network but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information?

If you wish to review, update or delete any personal information that we have collected about you, please contact us at [www.gamexn.com/ContactUs](http://www.gamexn.com/ContactUs). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

How Do I Learn About Changes To This Privacy Policy?

We may periodically update our Privacy Policy. Please understand that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently to remain informed about any changes to it. Your continued use of the GameXN Network will indicate your acceptance of any changes we do make. Our most current Privacy Policy will always be available for your review on secure.gamexn.net/en-US/PrivacyPolicy. 

How to contact us

We encourage your questions and comments about any privacy concerns, about this Privacy Policy, or about any of our products and services. Please direct them to us by using this submission form at: [gamexn.com/ContactUs](http://gamexn.com/ContactUs). 

© GameXN AS – Last updated: August 18, 2011

Copyright © 2013 [GameXN AS](http://gamexn.com/). All rights reserved. Terms of Service  
NOTICE: We may collect personal information on this site.  
To learn more about how we use your information, see our Privacy Policy.
